const movieQs = [{
    cat: "movie",
    type: 4,
    question: "The movie IN THE MOUTH OF MADNESS featured what fictional writer?",
    answers: ["Frank Mankin", "Sutter Cain", "Steven Cross", "Bob Newhart"],
}, {
    cat: "movie",
    type: 4,
    question: "Who played Dr. Hannibal Lecter in THE SILENCE OF THE LAMBS?",
    answers: ["Dustin Hoffman", "Sir Anthony Hopkins", "Sir Sean Connery", "Shaquiel O'Neil"],
}, {
    cat: "movie",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which Stanely Kubrick movie was banned in England until his death?",
    answers: ["Eyes Wide Shut", "A Clockwork Orange", "Full Metal Jacket", "The Killing"],
}, {
    cat: "movie",
    type: 4,
    question: "Bruce Lee's son, Brandon, died on the set of which film?",
    answers: ["Natural Born Killers", "The Crow", "Spice World", "Ip Man"],
}]

const musicQs = [{
    cat: "music",
    type: 4,
    question: "In 2019 this band release FEAR INOCULUM, their first album in thirteen years",
    answers: ["Metallica", "Tool", "The Spice Girls", "The Who"],
}, {
    cat: "music",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which artist won an Academy Award for THE SOCIAL NETWORK soundtrack and a Country Music Award for OLD TOWN ROAD?",
    answers: ["Lil Nas", "Trent Reznor", "Billie Eilish", "Billy Joel"],
    correct: 1,
}, {
    cat: "music",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which band created STAIRWAY TO HEAVEN?",
    answers: ["Journey", "Led Zeppelin", "Pink Floyd", "The Cure"],
}, {
    cat: "music",
    type: 4,
    question: "DONT STOP __________ is one of the best known songs from the band JOURNEY",
    answers: ["LIVING", "BELIEVING", "KEEP GOING", "IM CLOSE"],
}]


const geoQs = [{
    cat: "geo",
    type: 4,
    question: "What Continent is Mount Kilimanjaro located on?",
    answers: ["Asia", "Africa", "South America", "Europe"],
}, {
    cat: "geo",
    type: 4,
    question: "Where is the Isle of Man located?",
    answers: ["Red Sea", "Irish Sea", "Mediterranean Sea", "Aegean Sea"],
    correct: 1
}, {
    cat: "geo",
    type: 4,
    question: "What Continent is Cape Horn located on?",
}, {
    cat: "geo",
    type: 4,
    question: "What river runs through Baghdad?",
    answers: ["Nile", "Tigris", "Euphrates", "Jordan"],
}]


const spaceQs = [{
    cat: "space",
    type: 4,
    question: "How many gas giants are in our solar system?",
    answers: ["Two", "Four", "Three", "Six"],
}, {
    cat: "space",
    type: 4,
    question: "What is the closest star to our own?",
    answers: ["Betelguese", "Proxima Centauri", "Alpha Centauri", "Sirius A"],
}, {
    cat: "space",
    type: 4,
    question: "The moon called Titan orbits which planet?",
    answers: ["Venus", "Saturn", "Jupiter", "Mars"],
}, {
    cat: "space",
    type: 4,
    question: "One year on Jupiter is how many Earth years?",
    answers: ["Seven", "Twelve", "Ten", "Sixteen"],
}]


const codingQs = [{
    cat: "coding",
    type: 4,
    question: "In javascript, which is NOT an example of a loop",
    answers: ["for", "if else", "while", "do while"],
}, {
    cat: "coding",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which CSS element changes the size of text?",
    answers: ["text-size", "font-size", "size", "text"],
}, {
    cat: "coding",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which HTML element does NOT need a closing tag?",
    answers: ["main", "link", "title", "div"],
}, {
    cat: "coding",
    type: 4,
    question: "What does the FIRST O in OOP stand for?",
    answers: ["Oriented", "Object", "Other", "Obvious"],
}]


const lovecraftQs = [{
    cat: "lovecraft",
    type: 4,
    question: "One of Lovecrafts best known stories; The ________ Horror",
    answers: ["Cosmic", "Dunwich", "Lurking", "Innsmouth"],
}, {
    cat: "lovecraft",
    type: 4,
    question: "According to Lovecraft, Cthulhu lies sleeping on the bottom of the ocean in the city named:",
    answers: ["Atlantis", "R'lyeh", "Ab'oth", "Innsmouth"],
}, {
    cat: "lovecraft",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which Lovecraftian entitiy was the father of Wilbur Whatley?",
    answers: ["Cthulhu", "Yog-Sothoth", "Nub-Shiggurath", "Azathoth"],
}, {
    cat: "lovecraft",
    type: 4,
    question: "Charles _______ Ward was the subject of one of Lovecrafts stories.",
    answers: ["William", "Dexter", "Gaf-thy", "Abbott"],
}]


const historyQs = [{
    cat: "history",
    type: 4,
    question: "The assassination of this man sparked World War I",
    answers: ["Billy Joel", "Franz Ferdinand", "Pope Lazarus IV", "Boris Yeltsin"],
}, {
    cat: "history",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which year was Cleopatra believed to be born?",
    answers: ["560 BC", "69 BC", "143 BC", "42 AD"],
}, {
    cat: "history",
    type: 4,
    question: "Genghis Khans Reign took place during which century?",
    answers: ["Seventh", "Thirteenth", "Tenth", "Sixteenth"],
}, {
    cat: "history",
    type: 4,
    question: "What was the original name of Constantinople?",
    answers: ["Tripoli", "Byzantium", "Copenhagen", "Prague"],
}]


const religionQs = [{
    cat: "religion",
    type: 4,
    question: "In Norse Mythology, Odin's horse is named:",
    answers: ["Quetzalcoatl", "Sleipnir", "Jormungandr", "Nub Shiggurath"],
}, {
    cat: "religion",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which Titan was the father of Zeus?",
    answers: ["Themis", "Cronus", "Theseus", "Uranus"],
}, {
    cat: "religion",
    type: 4,
    question: "With Brahma and Vishnu, this god makes up the Hindu triumvirate",
    answers: ["Saraswati", "Shiva", "Kartikeya", "Ganesha"],
}, {
    cat: "religion",
    type: 4,
    question: "The Roman Goddess of wisdom, learning, arts, and industry:",
    answers: ["Vesta", "Minerva", "Ceres", "Diana"],
}]

const sportsQs = [{
    cat: "sports",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which sport is Gary Kasparov well known for?",
    answers: ["Tennis", "Chess", "Soccer", "Rugby"],
}, {
    cat: "sports",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which country did curling originate from?",
    answers: ["Sweden", "Scotland", "Russia", "Canada"],
}, {
    cat: "sports",
    type: 4,
    question: "Tualatin, Oregon hosts the West Coast Giant ________ Regatta",
    answers: ["Inner Tube", "Pumpkin", "Canoe", "Rowboat"],
}, {
    cat: "sports",
    type: 4,
    question: "______ of Legends is one of the worlds biggest e-sports.",
    answers: ["Story", "League", "Lash", "Gang"],
}]


const genQs = [{
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "Salvador Dalí had this animal as a pet",
    answers: ["Panda", "Anteater", "Koala", "Alligator"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "Area 51 is located in which US State?",
    answers: ["Utah", "Nevada", "New Mexico", "Arizona"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "How many colors are in a rainbow?",
    answers: ["Six", "Seven", "Eight", "Nine"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "What is Cynophobia the fear of?",
    answers: ["Ice", "Dogs", "Stairs", "Insects"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "What is the world's most expensive spice by weight?",
    answers: ["Melange", "Saffron", "Cinnamon", "Anise"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "What alcoholic drink is mainly made from juniper berries?",
    answers: ["Whiteclaw", "Gin", "Mead", "Vodka"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "When did the website FACEBOOK launch?",
    answers: ["2011", "2004", "2009", "2001"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "What’s the chemical symbol for silver?",
    answers: ["Mu", "Ag", "Sl", "Si"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "How many colors do the Olympic Rings have?",
    answers: ["Seven", "Five", "Four", "Six"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "What TV station did the show LOST originally air on?",
    answers: ["Fox", "ABC", "CBS", "NBC"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "What is the capital city of Australia?",
    answers: ["Melbourne", "Canberra", "Perth", "Sydney"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "How many notes are there in a musical scale?",
    answers: ["Five", "Seven", "Six", "Nine"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "A baby Oyster is called a :",
    answers: ["Chit", "Spat", "Oyling", "Dink"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "How many keys are there on a piano?",
    answers: ["94", "88", "76", "67"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which fictional hotel serves as the setting for THE SHINING?",
    answers: ["Bates", "Overlook", "Ritz Carlton", "California"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "What is the name of the time machine DOCTOR WHO uses?",
    answers: ["OCTDEX", "TARDIS", "PRIMER", "LOOMIS"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "Natasha Romanova is the real name of which superhero?",
    answers: ["Storm", "Black Widow", "Taskmaster", "Ms Marvel"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which year was Daniel Craig’s first Bond film released?",
    answers: ["2011", "2006", "2004", "2009"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "Which year did the European Union first introduce the Euro as currency?",
    answers: ["1992", "1999", "1985", "2006"],
}, {
    cat: "gen",
    type: 4,
    question: "Beirut is the capital of which country?",
    answers: ["Syria", "Lebanon", "Azerbaijan", "Croatia"],
}]